Guide to the Yale Divinity School Faculty Writings and Publications
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Faculty A-L
  - Kavanagh, Aidan, OSB
    - Musings from a Minefield, Reflection, 73/3, Mar 1976, pp. 5-7. (Box 16)
    - The Norm of Baptism: The New Rite of Christian Initiation of Adults, Worship, 48/3, pp. 143-152., n.d. (Box 16)
    - A Rite of Passage (portion of lecture delivered at the Theology Institute at Holy Cross Abbey, Canon City, Colorado in Aug. 1977) (Box 16)
    - Rules on Sexism and Its Ramifications for Christian Language. Taylor House Lecture, Feb 1979. (Box 16)
    - Pentecost 1, Proclamation 2, series a, Achtemeier, Krodel and Price, eds., (Philadelphia: Fortress Press, 1981). (Box 16)
    - Through Him, with Him, and in Him, U.S. Catholic, 41/8, Aug 1976, pp. 19-24. (Box 16)
    - Reflections from the Acting Dean, Reflections, 85/1, Winter 1990, p. 1. (Box 16)
    - LIst of publications.
  - Keck, Leander E.
    See Record Group No. 256.
  - Kelsey, David H.
    - Articles
      - Appeals to Scripture in Theology, Journal of Religion, 48/1, Jan 1968, pp. 1-21. (Box 17)
      - The Bible and Christian Theology, Jour. of the American Academy of Religion, XLVIII/3, 1979, pp. 385-402. (Box 17)
      - Hans Wilhelm Frei, In Memoriam, Service held Sept. 22, 1988 (Box 17)
      - Homosexuality and the Church: Theological Issues, Reflection, 80/3, Apr 1983, pp. 9-11. (Box 17)
      - Human Being, in Christian Theology: An Introduction to Its Traditions and Tasks, Hodgson and King, eds., 1982, pp. 141-167. (Box 17)
      - Jewish-Christian Dialogue and the Protestant Revolution, Conservative Judaism, 20/1, Fall 1965, pp. 44-50. (Box 17)
      - Method, Theological, in The Westminster Dictionary of Christian Theology, 1983, pp. 364-367. (Box 17)
      - Mind-Reading: Notes on the Basic Issues Program, written with Barbara G. Wheeler, Theological Education 20, no.2, Spring 1984, pp. 8-13. (Box 17)
      - Protestant Attitudes Regarding Methods of Biblical Interpretation, in Scripture in the Jewish and Christian Tradition: Authority, Interpretation, Relevance, 1982, pp. 134-161. (Box 17)
      - Reflections on Convocation '84: Issues in Theological Education, Theological Education, 1985 Spring, pp. 116- 138. (Box 17)
      - Scripture, Doctrine of, in the Westminster Dictionary of of Christian Theology, 1983, pp. 528-531. (Box 17)
      - Struggling Collegially to think about Evil: An Interpretive Essay, Occasional Papers, No. 16, 1981. (Box 17)
    - Book Reviews
      - Hartt, Julian N., Theological Method and Imagination, Journal of Religion, 58/4, 1978, pp. 428-435. (Box 17)
      - Reviews of his book The Fabric of Paul Tillich's Theology, in Theological Studies, 28/3, Sep 1967, pp. 567-568 and in Religion in Life, XXXVI/4, Winter 1967, pp. 626-628. (Box 17)
  - Kraeling, Carl H.
    - The Apocalypse of Paul and the 'Iranische Erlösungsmysterium'. Harvard Theological Review: July, 1931, pp. 209-244. (Box 17)
    - The Episode of the Roman Standards at Jerusalem. Harvard Theological Review: Oct., 1942, pp. 263-289. (Box 17)
    - A Greek Fragment of Tatian's Diatessaron from Dura, Studies and Documents, London: Christophers. (Box 17)
    - The Jewish Community at Antioch. Antioch Index Publications No. 1 (New Haven, 1932) pp. 130-160. (Box 17)
    - Olmstead's Chronology of the Life of Jesus. Anglican Theological Review: Oct., 1942, pp. 334-354. (Box 17)
    - The Sator Acrostic. Crozer Quarterly: Jan., 1945, pp. 28-38. (Box 17)
  - Latourette, Kenneth Scott
    See Record Group No. 3.
  - Lindbeck, George A.
    See Record Group No. 172.
  - Luccock, Halford
    - Religion as Social Passion, What Religion Means to Me, 1929. (Box 18)
    - Simeon Stylites Columns from the Christian Century, 1948- 1960 & Index. (Box 18)
    - Simeon Stylites Columns from the Christian Century, 1948- 1960 & Index. (Box 19)
    - Simeon Stylites Columns from the Christian Century, 1948- 1960 & Index. (Box 20)
    - Three letters from Luccock to James G. McLeod (YDS '29), 1929 (Box 20)
  - Lull, David J.
    - Articles
      - The Hope of Everlasting Life, YDS Advent Preaching Series, December, 1981. (Box 21)
      - Introduction, Semeia, 24, 1982. (Box 21)
      - "The Law Was Our Pedagogue": A Study in Galatians 3:19- 25, Journal of Biblical Literature, 1986, pp. 481-498. (Box 21)
      - The Servant-Benefactor as a Model of Greatness (Luke 22:24-30), Novum Testamentum, 1986, pp. 289-305. (Box 21)
      - The Spirit and the Creative Transformation of Human Existence, Journal of the American Academy of Religion, XLVII/1, Mar 1979, pp. 39-55. (Box 21)
      - To Set at Liberty: The Challenge of an Inclusive Language Lectionary, Reflection, 82/2, Jan 1985, pp. 21-24. (Box 21)
      - What is "Process Hermeneutics"?, Process Studies, 13/3, 1983, pp. 189-201. (Box 21)
    - Book Reviews
      - Brinsmead, Bernard Hungerford, Galatians - Dialogical Response to Opponents, in Interpretation, 39/1, Jan 1985, pp. 94-95. (Box 21)
      - Rhyne, C. Thomas, Faith Establishes the Law, Journal of Biblical Lit., pp. 301-303., n.d. (Box 21)
- Faculty M-W
  - McBride, S. Dean
    - Septuagint and Old Greek Versions: A Bibliography, 5 pp. (Box 21)
  - Macintosh, Douglas Clyde
  - Malherbe, Abraham J.
    - Articles
      - Abraham J. Malherbe as a New Testament Scholar: An Analysis and Appreciation, Part I: The Early Years. By John T. Fitzgerald. Restoration Quarterly: 42 (2004), pp. 163-200. (Box 21)
      - Ancient Epistolary Theorists. Ohio Jour. of Religious Studies: 5/2 (1977), pp. 3-77. (Box 21)
      - Antisthenes and Odysseus, and Paul at War. Harvard Theological Review, 76/2 (1983), pp. 143-173. (Box 21)
      - Apologetic and Philosophy in the Second Century. Restoration Quarterly, 7 (1963), pp. 19-32 (Box 21)
      - The Apologetic Theology of the Preaching of Peter. Restoration Quarterly, 13 (1970), pp. 205-223. (Box 21)
      - The Apostle Paul as a Pastor. In Jesus, Paul and John (Chinese University of Hong Kong, 1999), pp. 98-139. (Box 21)
      - Athenagoras on Christian Ethics. Journal of Ecclesiastical History, 20/1 (1969), pp. 1-5. (Box 21)
      - Athenagoras on the Location of God. Theologische Zeitschrift, (1970), pp. 46-52. (Box 21)
      - Athenagoras on the Poets and Philosophers. In KYRIAKON, Patrick Granfield and Josef A. Jungmann, eds., (Aschendorff, 1970), pp.214-225. (Box 21)
      - The Beasts at Ephesus. Journal of Biblical Literature, 87 (1968), pp. 71-80. (Box 21)
      - "Christ Jesus Came Into the World to Save Sinners": Soteriology in the Pastoral Epistles. InSalvation in the New Testament, van der Watt, Jan G., ed., (Brill 2005), pp. 331- 358. (Box 21)
      - The Christianization of a Topos (Luke 12:13-34). Novum Testamentum, 36 (1996), pp. 123-135. (Box 21)
      - Continuities in Scholarship: The Work of Nils Dahl. Reflection, Apr 1980. (Box 21)
      - Conversion to Paul's Gospel. In The Early Church in its Context: Essays in Honor of Everett Ferguson, Abraham J. Malherbe and Frederick W. Norris, eds., (Brill, 1998), pp. 230-244. (Box 21)
      - The Corinthian Contribution. Restoration Quarterly, v.3 (1959), pp. 221-233. (Box 21)
      - The Cultural Context of the New Testament: The Greco-Roman World. In The New Interpreter's Bible, vol VIII (Abingdon, 1995), pp. 12-26. (Box 21)
      - Determinism and Free Will in Paul: The Argument of 1 Corinthians 8 and 9. In Paul in His Hellenistic Context, T. Engberg-Pedersen, ed., (Fortress, 1994), pp. 231-255. (Box 21)
      - Did the Thessalonians Write to Paul? The Conversation Continues: Studies in Paul and John, Robert T. Fortna and Beverly R. Gaventa, eds., (Abingdon, 1990), pp. 246-257. (Box 21)
      - Early Christian Paraenesis in Context. In Beihefte zur Zeitschrift fuer die neutestamentliche Wissenshaft, (Walter de Gruyter, 2004) pp. 297-317. (Box 21)
      - Early Christianity and Society: A Contemporary Academic Interest. Chapter 5 in Freedom, Order and the University, James R. Wilbrun, ed., (Pepperdine University Press, 1982), pp. (Box 21)
      - Exhortation in First Thessalonian. Novum Testamentum, XX/3 (1983), pp. 238-256. (Box 21)
      - Godliness, Self-Sufficiency, Greed, and the Enjoyment of Wealth (1 Timothy 6:3-19): Part I,Novum Testamentum 52 (2010), pp. 376-405. (Box 21)
      - Godliness, Self-Sufficiency, Greed, and the Enjoyment of Wealth (1 Timothy 6:3-19): Part II,Novum Testamentum 53 (2011), pp. 73-96. (Box 21)
      - God's New Family in Thessalonica. In The Social World of the First Christians: Studies in Honor of Wayne A. Meeks, L. Michael White and L. O. Yarbrough, eds., (Fortress, 1995), pp. 116-125. (Box 21)
      - Gentle as a Nurse:The Cynic Background to 1 Thess ii. Novum Testamentum, XII (1970), pp.203-217. (Box 21)
      - Hellenistic Moralists and the New Testament. Rise and Decline of the Roman World, Wolfgang Haase and Hildegard Temporini, eds., (New York, 1992), pp. 267-333. (Box 21)
      - Herakles. Reallexikon Fur Antike Und Christentum, (1988), pp. 560-584. (Box 21)
      - The Holy Spirit in Athenagoras. The Journal of Theological Studies, 20 (1969), pp. 538-542. (Box 21)
      - The Household of God. Religion and Society, 4 (1971), pp. 17-24. (Box 21)
      - How to Treat Old Women and Old Men: The Use of Philosophical Traditions and Scripture in 1 Timothy 3. In Scripture and Traditions: Essays on Early Judaism and Christianity in Honor of Carl R. Holladay, P. Gray and G. R. O'Day, eds., (Brill, 2008), pp. 261-290. (Box 21)
      - "In Season and Out of Season": 2 Timothy 4:2. Journal of Biblical Literature, 103/2 (1984), pp. 235-243. (Box 21)
      - Inception of Christian Apologetics; Publication of Celsus' True Word; Emergence of "Theology" as a Concept; Crystallization of the New Testament. In Great Events from History, Frank N. Magill, ed., (1972), pp. 707-711; 731-736; 757-759; 779-783. (Box 21)
      - The Inhospitality of Diotrephes. In God's Christ and His People: Studies in Honor of Nils Alstrup Dahl, J. Jervell and W. Meeks, eds., (1977), pp. 222-232. (Box 21)
      - An Introduction: The Task and Method of Exegesis. Restoration Quarterly, 5 (1961), pp. 169-178. (Box 21)
      - Justin and Crescens. In Christian Teaching: Studies in Honor of LeMoine G. Lewis, E. Ferguson, ed., (1981), pp. (Box 21)
      - Medical Imagery in the Pastoral Epistles. In Texts and Testaments: Critical Essays on the Bible and Early Church Fathers, W. Eugene March, ed., 1980. (Box 21)
      - MH ENOITO in the Diatribe and Paul, Harvard Theological Review, 70 (1980), pp. 231-240. (Box 21)
      - New Testament, Traditions and Theology of Care. In Dictionary of Pastoral Care and Counseling, Rodney J. Hunter, ed., (Abingdon Press 1990), pp. 787-792. (Box 21)
      - "Not In a Corner": Early Christian Apologetic in Acts 26:26, The Second Century, 5/4 (1985), pp. 193-210. (Box 21)
      - On the Writing of Commentaries. Unpublished, n.d. (Box 21)
      - Overseers as Household Managers in the Pastoral Epistles. Unpublished, n.d. (Box 21)
      - 'Pastoral Care' in the Thessalonian Church. New Testament Studies, 36 (1990), pp. 375-391. (Box 21)
      - Paul: Hellenistic Philosopher or Christian Pastor?, Anglican Theological Review, (1986), pp. 3-13. (Box 21)
      - Paul's Self-Sufficiency (Philippians 4:11). Texts and Contexts, Tord Fornberg and David Hellholm, eds., (Scandinavian University Press, 1995), pp. 813-826. (Box 21)
      - Paulus Senex. Restoration Quarterly, 36 (1994), pp. 197- 207. (Box 21)
      - A Physical Description of Paul. Harvard Theological Review, 79:1-3 (1986), pp. 170-175. (Box 21)
      - A Physical Description of Paul. Christians Among Jews and Gentiles: Essays in Honor of Krister Stendahl on His Sixty-Fifth Birthday (Fortress Press, 1986), pp. 170-175. (Box 21)
      - A People Under the Word: Theological Interpretation. The Concept of the Believer's Church: Addresses from the 1967 Louisville Conference, (Herald Press, 1969), pp. 207-223. (Box 21)
      - Pseudo Heraclitus, Epistle 4: The Divinization of the Wise Man, Jahrbuch Für Antike und Christendom, 21 (1978), 22 pp. (Box 21)
      - Self-Definition among Epicureans and Cynics. In Jewish and Christian Self-Definition: Vol. 3,Self-Definition in the Greco-Roman World, 1982, pp. 46-59. (Box 21)
      - "Seneca" on Paul as a Letter Writer. The Future of Early Christianity, Birger A. Pearson, ed., (Fortress, 1991), pp. 414-421. (Box 21)
      - Social Level and Literary Culture. In Social Aspects of Early Christianity, (1977), pp. 29-59. (Box 21)
      - Soziale Ebene und Literarische Bildung. In Zur Soziologie des Urchristentums, W. Meeks, ed., 1979, pp. 194-221. (Box 21)
      - The Structure of Athenagoras, "Supplicatio Pro Christians." Vigiliae Christianae, 23 (1969), pp.1-20. (Box 21)
      - 1 Thessalonians as a Paraenetic Letter. pp. 1-26., n.d. (Box 21)
      - Towards Understanding the Apologists: A Review Article. Restoration Quarterly, 11 (1968), pp. 215-224. (Box 21)
      - The Virtus Feminarum in 1 Timothy 2:9-15. Reviewing Tradition: Studies in Texts and Contexts in Honor of James W. Thompson, M. W. Hamilton, ed., (Pickwick, 2006), pp. 45-65. (Box 21)
    - Reviews
      - Betz, Hans Dieter. Plutarch's Ethical Writings and Early Christian Literature. Journal of Biblical Literature ,100/1 (1981), pp. 140-142. (Box 21)
      - Koester, Helmut. Introduction to the New Testament. Religious Studies Review, 10 (1984), pp.112- 115. (Box 21)
  - Meeks, Wayne A.
    - Am I a Jew? Johannine Christianity and Judaism. pp. 163- 186. (Box 22)
    - And Rose Up to Play: Midrash and Paraenesis in 1 Cor. 10:1-22. JSNT, 16 (1982), pp. 159-169. (Box 22)
    - Christian Foolishness. Enquiry: March-May, 1971, pp. 22- 50. (Box 22)
    - The Christian Proteus. The Writings of St. Paul, pp. 435-445., n.d. (Box 22)
    - Examples of Hellenisti Biblical Literature: 1972, pp. 44-72. (Box 22)
    - Review of Galatians: A Commentary on Paul's Letter to the Churches in Galatia. Hans Dieter Betz. Journal of Biblical Literature, 20/2, June 1981, pp. 304-307. (Box 22)
    - The Social Context of Pauline Theology. pp. 266-277., n.d. (Box 22)
    - Understanding Early Christian Ethics. pp. 1-17. (Box 22)
    - Urban Environment of Pauline Christianity. pp. 1-10., n.d. (Box 22)
  - Meyer, Paul
    - A Note on John 10:1-18. Journal of Biblical Literature: 1956, pp. 232-235. (Box 22)
    - The Holy Spirit in the Pauline Letters: A Contextual Exploration. Interpretation, v. 23, Jan. 1979, pp. 3-18. (Box 22)
    - The Justification of Jesus. Shaffer Lectures, YDS, Feb. 1976, 117 pp. (Box 22)
    - The Problem of the Messianic Self-Consciousness of Jesus, reprinted from Novum Testamentum, Vol. IV, Fasc. 2, 1960, pp. 122-138. (Box 22)
  - Miller, Randolph Crump
    See Record Group No. 173.
  - Minear, Paul S.
    - Articles and Chapters
      - Adam and the Educator, Part 1, Christian Education, Vol. 12. May 1953, pp.204. (Box 54)
      - Adam and the Educator, The Christian Scholar, XXXIX/1, Mar 1956, pp. 6-18. (Box 56)
      - Adam und der Erzieher, Theologische Existenz Heute, K. G. Steck and G. Eicholz, eds., München, 1953, 38, pp. 34-52. (Box 56)
      - An Apocalyptic Adjective, Novum Testamentum, XII/2, 1970, pp. 218-222. (Box 56)
      - An Apostolic Structure of the Church, Andover Newton Quarterly, Jan 1966, pp. 15-37. (Box 56)
      - Audience Criticism and Markan Ecclesiology, pp. 79-89. (Box 56)
      - The Audience of the Fourth Evangelist. pp. 247-264., n.d. (Box 56)
      - J. S. Bach and J. A. Ernest: A Case Study in Exegetical and Theological Conflict, pp. 131-155. (Box 56)
      - Bach and Today's Theologians, Theology Today, XLII/2, Jul 1985, pp. 202-210. (Box 56)
      - Barth's Commentary on Romans, 1922-1972, Footnotes to a Theology: The Karl Barth Colloquium of 1972, M. Rumscheidt, ed., Suppl. to Studies in Religion, 1974, pp. 8- 19. (Box 56)
      - Behold I Make All Things New. A Bible Study with L. Vischer. World Council of Churches, Geneva, 1964. 32 pgs. (Box 56)
      - The Beloved Disciple in the Gospel of John, Novum Testamentum, XIX/2, pp. 105-123., n.d. (Box 56)
      - Between Two Worlds: Eschatology and History, Interpretation, V (1951), pp. 27-39. (Box 54)
      - Beyond the Ecumenical Dialogue, What?, Signs and Times of the Yale Divinity School, IV/4, Dec 1963, pp. 16-22. (Box 56)
      - Bible Studies, The Reformed World, 34/7-8, pp. 332-353., n.d. (Box 56)
      - Bible Study: Pictures of the Apostolic Church, Mid-stream, IV/4, Summer 1965, pp. 247-272. (Box 56)
      - The Biblical Sense of Community, The Journal of Religious Thought, I/2, Spring-Summer 1944. (Box 56)
      - Blasphemy Backdated, Horizons in Biblical Theology, Vol. 15, June 1993, pp. 38-51. (Box 54)
      - The Books That Shape Lives, The Christian Century, XCV/11, Mar 1978, p. 341. (Box 56)
      - Brahms' German Requiem, Theology Today, Jul 1965, pp. 236-249. (Box 56)
      - The Brahms' Requiem - Two Meditations, 1958. (Box 56)
      - But Whose Prayer Is It?, Worship, July 2002, pp. 324-338. (Box 54)
      - Catholicity in Practice, The Ecumenical Review, Oct 1962, pp. 39-44. (Box 56)
      - Christ and the Congregation: 1 Cor 5 and 6, Review and Expositor, LXXX/3, Summer 1983, pp. 341-350. (Box 56)
      - Christ, the Hope of the World. The Advisory Commission at Work. The Ecumenical Review, Oct 1953, pp. 1-9. (Box 56)
      - Christ, the Hope of the World. Bibliography, General Theological Library Bulletin, XLVI/3, Apr 1954, pp. 3-7. (Box 56)
      - Christian Eschatology and Historical Methodology, in Neutestamentliche Studien für Rudolf Bultmann, pp. 15-23. (Box 56)
      - The Christian Faith and Life Lessons: Unit VI - The Church Triumphant, Crossroads, 1/4, Jul-Sep 1951, pp. 9-20. (Box 56)
      - The Church in the World, Theology Today, XXVIII/1, Apr 1971, pp. 83-89. (Box 54)
      - The Church: Militant or Triumphant?, Andover Newton Bulletin, XLVII/3, Feb 1955, pp. 25-31. (Box 56)
      - The Conception of History, The Journal of Bible and Religion, XI/3, Aug 1943, pp. 156-161. (Box 56)
      - The Crucified World: The Enigma of Gal. 6:14, Theologia Crucis - Segnum Crucis: Festschrift für Erich Dinkler, G. Klein and C. Andresen, eds., 1979, pp. 395-407. (Box 56)
      - Dear Theo: The Kerygmatic Intention and Claim of the Book of Acts, Interpretation, XXVII/2, April 1973, pp. 131-150. (Box 57)
      - The Disciples and the Crowds in the Gospel of Matthew, Anglican Theological Review, Supplemental series/3, Mar 1974, pp. 28-44. (Box 57)
      - Diversity and Unity: A Johannine Case-Study, in Die Mitte des Neuen Testaments, U. Luz and H. Weder, eds., pp. 162- 175. (Box 57)
      - An Early Christian Theopoetic?, Semeia 12 The Poetics of Faith: Essays Offered to Amos Niven Wilder, 1978, pp. 201- 214. (Box 54)
      - Ecumenical Conversations. The North American Faith and Order Study Conference. Oberlin, Ohio. September 3-10, 1957. 48 pages. (Box 57)
      - False Prophecy and Hypocrisy in the Gospel of Matthew, Neues Testament und Kirche, pp. 76-93. (Box 57)
      - Far as the Curse is Found: the Point of Revelation 12:15-16, Novum Testamentum, XXXIII/1, 1991, pp. 71-77. (Box 57)
      - Form Criticism and Faith, Religion in Life, Winter, 1945-46, pp. 46-56., 1945-1946 (Box 57)
      - Die Funktion der Kindheitsgeschichten im Werk des Lukas, from DGS Lukas-Evangelium, 1974, pp. 204-235. (Box 57)
      - The Future of Ecumenical Miracles: A Perspective, Ecumenical Trends, 9/5, May 1980, pp. 73-74. (Box 57)
      - The Good News. Bible Studies on the Christian Mission, The Student Volunteer Movement, n.d. (Box 57)
      - Gospel History: Celebration or Reconstruction? in Jesus and Man's Hope, Pittsburgh Theological Seminary, 1970, Vol. 2, pp. 13-27. (Box 57)
      - A Grass-Roots Theology, Andover Newton Bulletin, 47/5, June 1955, pp. 20-22. (Box 57)
      - Guide to Personal and Family Devotion, Home Quarterly, 3/1, Jan-Mar 1944, pp. 19-3. (Box 57)
      - Guide to Personal and Family Devotion, Home Quarterly,3/4, Oct-Dec 1944, pp. 14-24. (Box 57)
      - Guide to Personal and Family Devotion, Home Quarterly, 4/1, Jan-Mar 1945, pp. 15-25. (Box 57)
      - Guide to Personal and Family Devotion, Home Quarterly, 4/2, Apr-Jun 1945, pp. 13-23. (Box 57)
      - Guide to Personal and Family Devotion, Home Quarterly, 4/3, Jul-Sep 1945, pp. 13-24. (Box 57)
      - He is Our Peace. Eight Bible Studies with L. Vischer. Week of Prayer for Christian Unity, 1963. Commission on Faith and Order. 34 pgs. (Box 57)
      - Heavens! The Reformed World, 32/6, June 1973, pp. 250- 256. (Box 57)
      - Historical Consciousness vs. Historical Knowledge, The Journal of Bible and Religion, VIII/2, May 1940, pp. 72-76. (Box 54)
      - The Holy and the Sacred, Theology Today, XLVII/1, Apr 1990, pp. 5-12. (Box 57)
      - The Holy Irritation of Renewal, Reflection, 64/3, Mar 1967, pp. 1-5. (Box 57)
      - The Home of the Our Father, Worship, 74 no 3 May 2000, p 212-222. (Box 54)
      - Homiletical Resources for the Season After Pentecost: the Gospel of John, Chapter 6, Review,5/2, Summer 1985, pp. 68-90. (Box 57)
      - The House of Living Stones: a Study of 1 Peter 2:4-12, Ecumenical Review, 34/3, Jul 1982, pp. 238-248. (Box 57)
      - How Objective is Biblical Criticism?, Journal of Bible and Religion, 9 no 4 N 1941, p 217-222. (Box 54)
      - Images of the Church in the New Testament, The South East Asia Journal of Theology, 1/2, Oct 1959, pp. 7-18. (Box 58)
      - The Import of Ecumenical Developments for Theological Education - A Protestant View, Theological Education, 3/2, Winter 1967, 308-316. (Box 58)
      - Inclusive Language and Biblical Authority, in Faith and History: Essays in Honor of Paul W. Meyer, J.T. Carroll et al, eds., 1991, pp. 335-351. (Box 58)
      - The Inclusive Language Lectionary, Presbyterian Outlook, 165/43, Dec 19-26, 1983, pp. 6-7. (Box 58)
      - The Influence of Karl Barth, Presbyterian Outlook, 169/1, Jan 5-12 1987, pp. 1 (excerpt from Minear's essay in How Karl Barth Changed My Mind, Donald K. McKim, ed.) (Box 58)
      - The Influences of Ecumenical Developments on New Testament Teaching, Jour. of Ecumenical Studies, 1971, pp. 286-299. (Box 58)
      - The Interpreter and the Birth Narratives, Symbolae Biblicae Upsalienses, 1950, pp. 3-22. (Box 58)
      - Interpreting the New Testament. Bibliography, General Theological Library Bulletin, XXXIX/1, Oct 1946. (Box 58)
      - An Introduction to Paul (pamphlet) Abingdon-Cokesbury Press, 82 p., n.d. (Box 58)
      - Jerusalem Ecumenical Institute, Theology Today, XXVIII/1, Apr 1971, pp. 83-89. (Box 58)
      - The Jerusalem Fund and Pauline Chronology, Anglican Theological Review, XXV/4, Oct 1943, pp. 389-396. (Box 58)
      - Jesus' Audience, According to Luke, Novum Testamentum, XVI/2, pp. 81-109., n.d. (Box 58)
      - Karl Barth (1886-1968), The New Republic, 160/5. Feb 1 1969, pp. 12-13. (Box 58)
      - Kierkegaard and the Bible. An Index with P. Morimoto. Princeton Theological Seminary. Princeton, N.J. 1953. 34 pgs. (Box 58)
      - Leitgedanken für Montreal, ökumenische Rundschau, 12/1, Jan 1963, pp. 1-11. (Box 58)
      - Leonard Bernstein: Theologian, Festschrift for Roger Hazelton, Andover Newton Quarterly, 17/4, Mar 1977, pp. 281-290. (Box 58)
      - Logos Ecclesiology in John's Gospel, Christological perspectives, p 95-111. New York: Pilgrim Press, 1982. (Box 54)
      - Luke's Use of the Birth Stories, Studies in Luke-Acts, Essays Presented in Honor of Paul Schubert, 1966, pp. 111-130. (Box 58)
      - Matthew, Evangelist and Johann, Composer, Theology Today, Oct 1973, pp. 243-253. (Box 58)
      - The Meeting Place, in Proceedings of the Ninth International Congregational Council, London, 1962, pp. 54-61. (Box 58)
      - The Messiah Forsaken...Why?, Horizons in Biblical Theology, 17 no 1 Je 1995, p 62-83. (Box 54)